1	John	John	NNP	PERSON	_	_
2	Smith	Smith	NNP	PERSON	_	_
3	is	be	VBZ	O	_	_
4	a	a	DT	O	_	_
5	student	student	NN	O	_	_
6	at	at	IN	O	_	_
7	Sussex	Sussex	NNP	ORGANIZATION	_	_
8	University	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	_	_
9	in	in	IN	O	_	_
10	the	the	DT	O	_	_
11	UK	UK	NNP	LOCATION	_	_
12	.	.	.	O	_	_

1	He	he	PRP	O	_	_
2	likes	like	VBZ	O	_	_
3	Coldplay	Coldplay	NNP	PERSON	_	_
4	.	.	.	O	_	_

